hello Scopus ed are you ready are you
ready okay we're doing a an update from
comma research for you guys
so I'm handing it off to editor and
Herald but I'm doing the filming
come on researchers off see this is
Connor research crew oh you know what I
should find it was too late but I should
have I should find a stabilizer it's
really cool oh my god if you're driving
at this very moment the E on me should
be paying attention we have drivers
monitoring really alright guys so coma
research has three things to tell you
right so the three announcements don't
read the board know like them so how
many people do you have we have 91 91 so
this is the timeline guys this is the
three priorities yeah so those are the
three things
waha beitia say Babesia it's like the
goatee or something all right so three
things that come on research is active
so coma research is not to desert it we
make projects so it's R squared the dill
and the 888 project so this is for you
guys to understand what we will be doing
right because we announced the coma
research but now we have to know what
come on research is going to be doing
and how is it different from call
product is it different
so the question because the first thing
that we want to make sure is that
research and coma
oh I all the research in other places
it's not a scam right usual research is
just this multi-level marketing campaign
where you just like the research publish
papers go to go first so you can hire
more researchers and your company can
look all right until you hire real
workers that do all the job mm-hmm so
common research is different by the fact
that the research also makes real things
here on this R square we will be doing
are you breaking common research yes
people are saying where's the stream at
it what's happening are we not live
someone responds with notes fine okay
okay okay well once that one final
question should I landscape it for you
guys yeah so what are you guys for firm
all right this is a secret it's just
laggy Holly because I'm backing up my
phone at the same time okay we're ready
okay so our square do you guys
understand us where can we go to the
next one
yeah so our square of one of the things
that our square is gonna do for you have
you guys heard about the big model you
been here dude everyone knows that big
model everyone knows about big mall but
there are the issues about the big mall
right the big boulders big entrance a
lot of energy so one of the things that
our square is gonna do is this stilll
whatever big mobile knows into a small
model so it's model drugs just as good
as big model so that's one of the things
there wow yeah big deal yeah no no
Oh big deal okay big deal is the deal so
what did what is the deal no they'd have
to understand this valve okay no I'm not
joking
yeah this is this mm-hmm exactly so
here's orange as a deal you see how
important to do is because they do get
some like a lot of space on that no that
makes no sense you need to explain what
no it doesn't matter it gets a lot of
space and this is important that's what
matters
orange no you're talking about literal
space yeah there's gonna be a quiz at
the end so you know the bill is stands
for the driving intermediate layer or
language or language it's what guys so
you have to understand this because this
is pretty much the future oh no
seriously listen listen listen stop stop
right there okay deal no big deal
is what is a second driving car right a
self-driving car is a three pieces piece
of technology right it's that humor it's
the car itself and it's the AI and each
one of them speaks a different language
the human doesn't think of like how much
accelerate how much I want to steer now
the human nose I want to get there this
fast right and you a car
is this mechanical thing that is done
and then there's daily act which is the
software each one of them speaks
different language and then you have a
bunch of blue code that communicates
them the dill is here to solve that the
language between the car and the AI and
we have a lived some weeks weekend
little bit I know but it my phone
accidentally went quickly
okay well show you someone wait ready
dopey boom oh this is the you know the
debug so this is the dill right here
mm-hmm this is kind of what we expect to
be the common language between the car
and the AI so it just goes through like
where the lanes the red shows you where
the driving limit is so you clearly
don't want to drive in the trees so
that's where the the red lines separates
that when the orange is the lanes and
lane markings and then the yellow is
where the other cars are from the radar
so the idea is that we can make a model
that will be able to you know generate
these types of this type of
representation of the world as you can
see on the right and that should be
enough to be able to control the car yes
and navigate yeah you look at that you
know exactly where your room is so does
the AI so that's a car
we are leaking secrets mostly that's
enough that's enough you're right you
don't want to look too much into
surprises yeah yeah okay so that's the
deal guys that this is the common
language so and here here goes the
question why do you want to build this
unified language right so if you are a
person and you understand where a
self-driving car is doing so it's too
safe if you are a customer electronic
company like Samsung wherever or
something and you want your copper your
devices student look understand
self-driving cars to understand right
now well you can drive the car you have
to spit the deal and if you are an OPM
if you are
car company and you want your car to
interface with this common language
there's gonna be bass Tanner it's gonna
be you don't understand how big this is
gonna be but but yeah I feel guests can
understand you guys recently but today
if today you want to start speaking
they'll if you think your company should
start speaking the deal you guys should
call Ricardo Ricardo Sarna CEO everybody
knows Ricardo so follow up with Ricardo
is be more than happy been his email is
viv at common dad I am so the last thing
that we have to tell them but not least
is the Aiden a product unfortunately we
cannot leak the full meaning of what a
deviated stance
yeah but 88 projects about HD maps and
we all know how how much you guys are
excited about HTML so we can announce
that there will be data lots of data big
data
Aaron wants to make sure you guys
understand it it's very big and there's
also open source software with big data
because just data's cheap without
software right guys so there will be a
lot of data and here I want to show you
guys a little bit of what this thing is
gonna look like
so the idea of making self-driving cars
HD maps is by making sure your car can
understand how far away things are right
so we are working on right now we want
to work on but we are working something
for you guys which is that vision for
young so we'll have that vision for you
this is a young image and precisely this
image not that one but some other image
there is some where and then I have a
bunch of visualizations don't worry
about it so there is this one here and
this one I know exactly where the image
is
got a clique damages you guys are gonna
see the images so an image like this
this is what a regular young you can see
yeah
and business and young with 3d vision
Wow so yeah humans of that well yeah so
they aliens gonna be able to see in 3d
you're gonna be able to see how far away
things are and that goes into the dill
right because the deal understands
distance the deal understand but that
also goes into the HD maps and that goes
into they attain a project and if you
want to make sure by the way EDA is
about open source data right and beauty
HD maps here's one thing about beauty
hmm what's the point of working out by
the way huh what's the point of radar
now what is the point of razor 7s what
is the point of radar well radar and
things like radar and radar can help us
know how our crazy are so we know that
we heard at least just as good as them
and later we are better than them yeah
yeah
so you know you finish your presentation
we'll take questions at the end that's
okay yeah so here's one thing here's one
thing the alien a project is about
releasing data right data for HD maps
data for HD maps is about knowing the
distance between objects in the camera
and also knowing the distance between
two views of the road so if you have
something like this like these are
different routes on that people driving
the car they are open pilot in different
days right
and then we know how close those images
are and then we try to match them how
far away is this camera from this camera
to this camera here's one thing if you
guys want to make sure you're part of
this data we introduce you a concept
called common raid which is about
several okoma
Ian's driving on a single highway well
you don't have times that I wasn't
that's way more exciting wait wait wait
but if you do something like this let us
know this is not mandatory we'll figure
it out a way to do it without this but
if you want to make sure your data goes
into the ADA a project you want to get
your buddies in your common meetups and
drive together down the highway
preferably with a different ways and why
this is a thing because it's this this
is the kind of images we are looking for
to build a date if you if you drive in
the same place with other people even
without using your pen pilot just even
with great panda you increase your
chances of going into this data set of
having this data in the big open data
set for for the world because then there
is no elimination problem right
everybody's ready at the same time of
the day you make sure your data goes
into this into this data set this is
something we were building for you guys
to make sure you guys through part of
the research just as far as you are of
the product so multiple cards not
multiple eons in one card multiple cars
yeah just go to the same server and then
you know it's about it's about complete
quest with your friends
it's about completing quests together if
you put multiple we use on your same
cards to a long yeah but it's something
much social it's nice okay so let me
yeah that's real good the three Nelson
let's let's add one more announcement
because we have 96 viewers and I'm
organizing the self-driving car tour I
don't really I appreciate that more than
you never know this um I don't know but
we are planning on stopping let's say I
let's put this here
okay we are planning I wish I could just
put you guys somewhere but I can't okay
we'll just hold the crew like this we
were planning on stopping in la la fenix
Albuquerque or Santa Fe wherever you
beds aren't let us know potentially
Oklahoma City someone said they were
near there Dallas and New Orleans so you
guys should let let us know message me
on slack or email me Vince at common dot
a I if you are in one of those areas
want to help organize and meet up
because we're coming your way with a
self-driving car tour and we'll have
merch first sale only on that tour okay
questions for this good houston yes
short wherever o as long as it's on the
way from SF to New Orleans I've never
been acute and I'd love to go so yeah
Houston sounds good message me I'm
Julius have questions about what was
just an ask though we've got all the
time say what's going on sound is fine
that okay that should tell them about
better room yeah yeah yeah sure okay so
yours no no let's not show ya you should
love them we shouldn't let them see when
it's ready right yes I just saw like all
rigged dot that stuff when it's ready
yeah behind this room is a whole lot of
secrets that we actually really can't
share
yeah we'll share when it's ready okay
that's better so okay what format will
HD landscape delivered on huh what
format will HD Maps be delivered on
there's gonna be a bunch of pictures and
there is gonna be a lot there's gonna be
several images the GPS tracks
annotations about how much you want
camera from one image change to the
other switch size software that makes
room is so yeah that's we plenty they a
day to be like the vs. staff over
building the ultimate highway driving
research data set so can they access the
maps if they're non yon user can be s
the maps access it access them oh the
map is gonna be open source the bet is
gonna be for everybody
yeah good editor say we're using a depth
net if I were using a bathmat
yes we are training a bathmat and we
will have the can't do we will have on a
mural metric to predict depth and
distance is from product okay so yeah
it's gonna be software based app by the
way do you guys like this image it's
pretty great right we had all the old
actors come back so George could get an
actual photo shoot with them okay George
is part of the research team is working
don't you know he's behind the store
maybe we can't tell you will we
recognize science and traffic lights but
we do a lot of the key before the end of
the years
come through the window
okay yes what else what else what else
what else
traffic and traffic lights and stop
signs by the end of the year is that
going to be happening talk more about
how the 3d view was generated okay so
the tritium fusion really like this so
you have two images yeah I mentioned do
have some image and oh oh my gosh
it's a it's a really good place this is
your computer
I know it's fine let's turn it off okay
holy now Arab you take care of you
and they'll be like am I really
oh my god okay I hope it's an eye bar L
weak that wasn't even planned holy
yeah yeah okay that's fine that's amore
oh that's that's what I already filmed
you are so right that's there it goes
okay so they know they see one another
yes you a little death are estimated
from cam yeah yeah okay so you have to
understand how to transform one
dimension to the other when you're
driving your car or when you have you
and your board is on a common raid we
ask the software how to just one one
image into the other so the way it does
is it predicts how far away each pixel
is from the camera so it projects all
this pixels in 3d and then he estimate
the distance between the two cameras and
then regenerate the the new image from
the new point of view then it compares
to the to the second pair of image so a
useful metric
why not using dual camera we're not
using it ever yeah that's one way of
doing it so we're looking at into the
duo
technology but but when you have when
you drive several times over the same
Road that's the same you dual cameras
right by the price of one so yeah whoa
came our technology but if they only
wants can we use more cars with schipper
plus with grey or similar can we use Y
it more cars that are not exact
oh here for us so they want to have
shipper plus yes that was good
Panda no no no I see can we match
navigate on autopilot with our current
card where can we match Oh sounds like
stuff oh he wants to be guys just have
food you're getting your hair cut
what are you getting that's a compliment
cause headaches are good it's about his
hair good for the past like two weeks I
know I didn't but you mention it a lot
no I didn't do you have you really have
perhaps okay I got my haircut in Brazil
guys yeah that's the place of where
everything beautiful comes from okay
here's what you guys don't understand
the Navigator without a pilot is just
like a cheaper version of the deal the
deal is like the real thing if you
understand where the road is if you
understand what the growth is and you
your car the eye everything speaks the
same language people whatever you want
well that's that that's the whole point
of the deal by the way guys dad you guys
do the best you can at Tesla just did
you like how how how cute is their copy
of shiver did they got a shifter it's
kind of cute right it's it comes after
shiver and then I'll tell has a fish
came to this is such a thing that you
and George both say you call things cute
it's like Mazda meaningly kind of thing
you know oh it's a ice is this nice so
maybe well two years later the bitter -
came to you so maybe two years from now
there will also be called Tesla rates I
don't know George is in this closet we
already told you that Tesla steering
lane change in traffic predictions -
well traffic predictions we don't have
traffic signs on the deal oh what a guy
saw right there is like four
is the original version which is just
like a translation of whatever we have
or right now on our copilot open pilot
in a way that is do compliance so we're
just changing a little bit the API so
does DISA standard is the language right
then we are planning to be future ready
and we would traffic lights exit
everything that all that will be on not
written until because in cars if you
want your car to understand you have to
be speaking do ya know RPC didn't catch
on fire it was at your Vermont a wasn't
in Minnesota so shout out to your before
not ruining computers yeah one still at
a time by the way here we're looking for
sponsorships for self-driving roadtrip
so if you guys want to reach out to me
you're Bramante folks if any of you guys
are out there I know I am fast about
banning emojis it's better cooling our
RGB cameras the only perception sensors
being utilized yes yeah you can consider
that perception see since like radar
yeah the curing cars have radar to you
right yeah what else yeah it's our
deepest one yeah call er to be plus plus
guys because it's not only our GBD right
the dimness condition they all said you
need some understand speech so it's hard
to be possible that's not I thought
there's a band question to what is the
very where did this guy sleeves go for
real
show them the back with each other with
the back - oh this is them know this is
the old commerce I guys yeah when I was
G intern yeah I was here in 2016 and
then they would make me wear this oh we
are gonna be so ripped okay could we run
Dooley on technology if we wanted to
slash have no friends if you want to
have no no if they want to slash they
have no fresh oh ok so just for now you
just drive over and over yeah
a couple of times and that's the same
thing as a dual cannon boom even cheaper
but don't worry guys
we know how much you guys love the dual
wield technology we'll have somebody to
figure it out
probably heroin whenever there is a hard
question I say hero please get it for me
I know how to use it for a really nice
reason and in heroine is the genius so
kind yeah with Michael I by the way do
we are you selling chains no no no oh
wait you guys me a culture do you know
how hot so we are doing , swag
exclusively for this tour so maybe we'll
so we'll bring back the tank top but to
be honest there you know I'm not the
biggest fan at all oh I like that idea
kama crops yeah yeah yeah the comic
craft shop but you guys just so you know
there are spiders on sale for $69.99 or
69 I think at six nine dollars on sale
right now at shop comma Dada a they are
they were recently released very few
people now igniter okay guys yes someone
literally just said I'm bored that's
great then log off your hoodie amazing
middle spins and now we have to go back
we're gonna work yeah you guys probably
yeah perfect okay by scobie's we'll see
you all for joining us
yes